#### Contact

ckuhn12388@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/charlie-kuhn-b97597125 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Critical Care

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

#### Languages

English

#### Certifications

Registered Nurse

**CRRT** 

BLS

**ACLS** 

#### Honors-Awards

Daisy award nominee

# Charlie Kuhn

Travel Nurse at Atlas MedStaff Reno, Nevada

## Summary

After graduating with my ASN, Indiana University Hospital offered me a wonderful position on the Transplant Intensive Care Unit. I got to spend 4 years and gain experience in this high acuity, fast paced, ICU at Indiana University Hospital; I was proud to be a part of such an amazing, skilled, compassionate and hard working transplant team. I hope to find the same once I make my move to Reno Nevada. My current plans involve finishing out my contract at IU health. And continue to explore travel nurse opportunities as well as permanent jobs to gain experience with a variety of ICU patients and further my skill level as a Registered Nurse. Currently I am working towards my CCRN and will pursue my BSN.

Indiana University Hospital Transplant specializes in Liver, Pancreas, Kidney/Pancreas, Liver/Kidney, Kidney, Intestine, and Multi-Visceral transplants. The ICU manages patients that are pre-transplant, post-transplant, and those in multi-organ failure and sepsis. IU Health Transplant is one of the few transplant centers in the U.S. performing intestine and multi-visceral transplants involving more than one organ and with great outcomes.

IU Health is also among one of the top transplant programs in the nation according to the Organ Procurement and Transplantation Network (OPTN).

I now have 2 years experience in the Surgical Trauma ICU world as a Travel ICU RN. I have also 2 years experience in the Medical/Neuro ICU. I have worked multiple Level 1 trauma centers around the US as well as level 2 and 3. I have gained wonderful experience thus far and continue to pursue new travel opportunities and currently considering permanent positions!

Currently on assignment in Indianapolis IN at my home hospital IU health University Hospital on the Medical ICU until September.

## Experience

Atlas MedStaff 3 years 10 months

Travel Nurse
June 2020 - Present (1 month)
IU health University Hospital

Travel ICU RN September 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Travel Nurse July 2019 - May 2020 (11 months) Renown

**Fusion Medical Staffing** 

3 years 3 months

Travel Registered Nurse
April 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)
ICU Travel Nurse

CVICU/MICU Travel RN April 2019 - July 2019 (4 months) Chesterfield, Missouri

Renown Health Travel Registered Nurse April 2018 - March 2019 (1 year) Reno, Nevada

UNC Health Care Travel ICU RN January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months) Smithfeild NC

Johnston Health ICU

Hartford Hospital
Travel RN for Fusion -Surgical Trauma ICU
April 2017 - December 2017 (9 months)
Hartford, Connecticut

Vidant Medical Center Surgical/Neuro trauma ICU December 2016 - March 2017 (4 months)

Greenville, North Carolina

Amarillo, Texas Area

909 bed, level 1 trauma hospital.

Northwest Texas Healthcare Surgical/Neuro trauma RN-travel RN Atlas Medstaff September 2016 - December 2016 (4 months)

Level 3 trauma hospital. Surgical trauma ICU, care of neuro trauma and a variety of post surgical patients.

IU Health University Hospital 4 years 2 months

Critical Care RN
August 2012 - September 2016 (4 years 2 months)
Indianapoilis IN

Charge RN-Transplant ICU, CRRT trained, care of pre and post, Liver, Kidney, Liver/Kidney, Kidney/Pancreas, Pancreas, multi-visceral transplant, patients in multi-organ failure and sepsis.

Critical Care RN
August 2012 - September 2016 (4 years 2 months)
Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Charge RN, CRRT trained, care of pre and post, Liver, Kidney, Liver/Kidney, Kidney/Pancreas, Pancreas, multi-visceral transplant, patients in multi-organ failure and sepsis.

Elks Lodge 1188
Bartender/ waitstaff
April 2010 - May 2012 (2 years 2 months)
Robinson Illinois

Best Western Robinson Inn Housekeeper March 2007 - April 2010 (3 years 2 months) Robinson Illinois

Education

Illinois Eastern Community Colleges-Lincoln Trail College Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2012)